Hello, I'm Johnny Cash.
It's rolling round the bend
Since I don't know when
Keeps a rollin'
My mama told me, "Son"
Don't ever play with guns"
Just to watch him die
That whistle blowin'
I got another 15.
Not today, you don't.
You're up.
You know the deal.
Successfully complete
the mission,
you get ten years
off your sentence.
You fail to follow my orders
in any way
and I detonate
the explosive device
Good dog.
We are
a black ops unit.
Meaning, nothing you see here
ever happened.
Savant.
Your commanding officer
Or would you
rather be called Durlin?
I'd rather not
be called at all.
But I'll do anything
to get out of this hellhole.
Well,
welcome to "anything."
So this is
the famous Suicide Squad.
Well, we consider
that term degrading.
The official term
is "Task Force X."
And love 'em or hate 'em,
these are your brothers and
sisters for the next few days.
Oh!
Whoa.
Captain Boomerang.
Blackguard.
Mongal.
Javelin.
T.D.K.
Weasel.
And, of course...
Hey, guys, sorry I'm late.
Had to go number two.
Hmm, good to know.
Flag.
Oh, sorry. Comin' through.
Hey, Boomer.
What are you doing back
in prison, Harls?
I got road rage. In a bank.
-Oh. So sorry. Comin' through.
-Turn it around. There. No.
-There? Here?
Put it in there.
Now you're safe.
All right.
Thanks, man.
Prepare for liftoff.
And away we go.
Harley and T.D.K...
- Digger.
...have they worked
together before?
Not yet. I'm excited.
What does
Savant do again?
It's Brian Durlin.
He's an expert in weapons
and hand-to-hand combat.
Yeah, well, I'm putting 20
on him that he's gonna bite it.
Me too. And Weasel,
-Boomer and Mongal.
- Yeah, I think...
Is Mongal an alien
or some type of god?
-What are you doing?
-Oh. Hey.
Just making sure
everything was ready to go.
Good meeting, everybody.
Just our normal,
casual morning meeting.
Yeah, I just gotta, uh,
do this thing.
Nothing weird about it.
Okay.
- Oh, yeah.
Flag.
Yeah, we're T-minus five
from the drop.
Get the whole team safely
to that beach, Colonel.
You will receive
further orders once there.
We're in
a butcher's freezer, Harls,
surrounded by dead hogs
hangin' on hooks.
Only they don't know it yet.
Leave him alone, Boomer.
What does T.D.K. stand for?
What?
Your name is T.D.K., correct?
Yeah.
And it stands for what?
It stands for me.
It's what a name is.
Your name is letters?
All names are letters,
dickhead.
I love your accent.
American women
all love accents.
We do.
'Cause we don't got none.
-Yo, is this a dog?
-What?
Is this thing a dog?
-A... A dog?
-Yes.
What kind of dog
do you think it is, mate?
I don't know, I'm not familiar
with all the breeds.
I'm gonna go with Afghan Hound.
Since when does an Afghan
Hound have bloody thumbs?
Oh, my God, is it a werewolf?
I've wanted to meet
a werewolf forever.
Yo, they sat me
next to a werewolf?
That's not right.
Yo, let me out.
I do not fuck with werewolves.
Hey, hey,
he's not a werewolf, okay!
He's a weasel. He's harmless.
I mean, he's not harmless,
he's killed 27 children,
but, you know, we got him to...
I think he's agreed to do this.
Whatever the case,
just everyone
get into position to drop.
Did anyone check
on whether Weasel could swim?
The Weasel is dead! I repeat,
-the Weasel is dead.
Northeast, all clear.
Approach the shore.
Over.
Savant, hold your position.
Roger that.
Amateurs.
Waller, we're
on the beach and dry.
-Blackguard. Get down, you...
-Hey, guys! Hey.
...there's fucking soldiers
everywhere!
You can come out now,
it's just me.
What the fuck
is Blackguard doin'?
I'm the one who contacted you.
Is this what's supposed
to happen? What the fuck?
Blackguard, get back
into your position.
Look, look.
I brought everybody, look.
They're right behind me.
Whoa. Hey.
Hey, guys. Whoa.
We got a deal, right?
Uh... Uh...
Waller, we're made.
I'm the one who called you.
Blackguard sold us out.
He contacted the fucking
Corto Maltese Army!
Waller, we need to retreat.
Negative, Flag.
The mission is too important.
This is a tough group.
-You can make it.
-Okey-doke.
Waller, with all due respect,
we're in the middle
of a goddamn... Harley, wait!
Whoo-hoo!
Zero-two-two-seven
is wide open.
Colonel, dispatch
-The Detachable Kid.
-T.D.K., two o'clock!
T.D.K. is "The Detachable Kid"?
What the fuck?
I didn't pick the damn team!
Don't worry, Flag,
I got the bird.
-Mongal! Don't.
-Huh?
Strewth!
Boomer!
Savant is off the rails.
Savant, turn back.
-Savant.
Savant, I'm warning you,
this is desertion.
Savant!
This is your last chance.
Turn back around.
You are in violation
of your agreement!
Oh, please! No.
Damn it.
How's Team Two holding up?
Team Two, check.
Set point bravo.
All troops on the south beach
are engaged.
Team Two is clear to go
on the north beach.
Congratulations, Bloodsport.
How'd you do it, Waller?
There's no soldiers out here
on patrol at all.
Let's
just say they were distracted.
He was twelve years old
On East Two-nine
When she pulled the plug
Fourteen years old
When he died
Who died, died
And just died
Let their gimmicks go rotten
In upper Manhattan
Bullet in the head
On the night that he was wed
Two more friends of mine
Who died, died
And they died
From a hotel room
From a cell in The Tombs
In the jugular vein
More than all the others
Who died, died
For the road
To wear that heavy load
Of Baudelaire before
Oh, jeez.
Oh.
Here you go, champ.
Excuse me.
Who the fuck is Bloodsport?
Robert DuBois.
A world-class marksman.
In his hands,
anything is a deadly weapon.
His father was a mercenary
who trained his son to kill
from the moment he was born.
He's in prison for putting
Superman in the ICU
with a kryptonite bullet.
-DuBois?
-Same answer as the last time.
Piss off.
I'm not joining your goddamn
Suicide Squad.
We'll see.
You have a visitor.
They said you got in trouble.
I stole.
You stole what?
-A style watch.
-A star latch?
A style watch.
You can watch TV on it.
Why would you want to
watch TV on your watch?
I don't know.
Next time you want
to nick something,
you take a partner,
and they can be your lookout.
That's your advice?
Yeah.
You're a terrible father.
Hey, I didn't ask
to be a father
You make that perfectly clear.
Your mother sprung
that one on me.
Well, she's not around anymore,
so you can lay off
of her, okay?
Oh, I tried to lay off her,
but then she dragged out
the paternity test.
-Fuck you!
-No, fuck you!
Fuck you!
I can't believe
you don't care that I stole,
only that I got caught!
I don't only care
that you got caught,
I care that you got caught
for stealing
something as stupid
as a fucking TV watch!
It does other things too!
But nothing that your phone
can't fucking do!
It's embarrassing!
No, what's fucking embarrassing
is having you as my father.
Yeah, well, I told you, Tyla,
when I came here
that any goodness
I ever had in me had been
wrung out bare by my old man.
And I also told you to go out
there and do your own thing
and stay far away
from me or anyone like me,
didn't I?
So, why are you here
when you and I both know
I have nothing good
to offer you?
Because my court date
is coming up,
and Miss Waller said
maybe you could help me out.
To get me to lead
your shite fucking mission,
you're gonna send
my 14-year-old daughter
No.
Your daughter is 16, DuBois.
You're a real
father of the year.
Fine. You know what,
Tyla needs to grow up anyway
'cause she's a little ditzy
like her fucking mother.
So, a year in juvie,
no fucking problem.
Not juvie. Being 16
in the state of Louisiana
means that
under the right circumstances,
she could be tried as an adult.
And, if convicted,
could be sent right here
to old Belle Reve.
And in here, well, you never
know what might happen
to a frail young thing
like that.
Shames me to say
that we have
the highest mortality rate
in the entire
U.S. prison system.
Whoa, hey, hey, hey!
You're threatening
my fucking daughter!
I'm protecting this country.
-Everyone stand down.
-Miss Waller, I...
Stand down!
I wouldn't take
such extreme measures...
Oh, extreme?
Oh, yeah, a little extreme.
...if this mission
weren't more important
than you could
possibly imagine.
Fuck your mission.
You have the military
experience necessary,
and everything in your
psychological profile tells me
you have what it takes
to be a leader.
No, I'm no fucking leader!
Then I'll make you one.
Are you in or out?
Good. Let's meet your team.
-Come on.
-Fuck me, man.
Let's go.
She was gonna kill his kid?
Each member
of the team is chosen
for his or her own completely
unique set of abilities.
This is Christopher Smith,
known as Peacemaker.
In his hands,
anything is a deadly weapon.
His father was a soldier
who trained his son
how to kill from the moment
he was born.
-Are you having a laugh?
-What?
You just said each member
of the team is chosen
for their unique abilities.
He does exactly what I do.
But better.
I always hit
my targets dead center.
I hit them more in the center.
Well, you can't hit something
more in a center.
-I use smaller bullets.
-What?
They go inside
your bullet holes
without even touching the side.
Next up is King Shark.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
Some people claim
that Nanaue is a descendant
of an ancient shark god.
Whatever the case,
he's strong and deadly.
Does it talk?
Book read.
Book's upside-down.
See that? It's pretending
to read a book.
So smart, me.
Enjoy book so much.
Be a mite careful,
as he's developed a taste
for human meat.
Huh?
Next, we have Cleo Cazo,
-Ratcatcher 2.
-Settle down!
Ooh.
What, we couldn't
afford Ratcatcher 1?
He's dead.
This is his daughter.
Cazo, will you be joining us?
I just woke up.
I don't function well
early in the morning.
My deepest apologies
for disturbing you.
Hmm, it's all right.
-Get your ass out here!
Millennials.
Oh, no way.
-That's not coming with us.
-She controls rats.
I know, I caught that.
It's a disgusting superpower.
This is Sebastian.
Say hello, Sebastian.
I'm not shakin' the rat's hand.
And finally,
we have Abner Krill.
What's that 'round his neck?
A power dampener.
They call him
the Polka Dot Man.
Polka Dot Man.
What's he do,
throw polka dots at people?
He does.
He throws polka dots at people.
Hey, Polka Dot Man,
I was hoping you'd entertain
my kid's birthday party.
You fucking pussy!
-These are soldiers?
We need to debrief.
Fuck.
Corto Maltese
is a small island nation off
the coast of South America.
Over the past 100 years,
the country has been ruled
with an iron fist
by the Herrera family.
But, a week ago, this guy,
General Silvio Luna,
along with his right-hand man,
Mayor General Mateo Suarez,
took control of
the Corto Maltese government
in a violent military coup.
The entire Herrera family were
hanged in a public execution.
Although the United States
did not condone
the excesses
of the Herrera regime,
they were non-antagonistic
toward the U.S.
Luna, however,
is virulently anti-American.
So, you want us to kill Luna?
No.
This is Jotunheim.
A scientific
experimentation facility
containing something known only
as Project Starfish.
Our intelligence sources
tell us
that Starfish
is extraterrestrial in origin.
In the hands
of the Luna regime,
it is potentially cataclysmic
for Americans and the world.
Your mission
is to infiltrate Jotunheim
and destroy every trace
of Project Starfish.
How are we supposed to get in?
Gaius Grieves, the Thinker,
is a geneticist in charge
of Project Starfish.
After hours, he hangs out
at a gentlemen's club
known as La Gatita Amable.
Get Grieves to help you
by whatever means necessary
and he can get you
into Jotunheim.
Any questions?
What is that?
That is
an overhead projector.
Do you ever use it anymore?
No, not really.
So, why don't you
just throw it away?
Peacemaker?
Starfish is a slang term
for a butthole.
Think there's any connection?
No.
No...
Nanaue.
...connection.
Hand.
Yes, that is your hand,
Nanaue, very good.
We're all gonna die.
I hope so.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Control, we have a disturbance
south of here.
It's just
a diversion, Bloodsport.
All right,
we cut through the jungle
Don't they have blockades
at the city limits?
That's the word.
How we getting in? Especially
with Charlie the Tuna here.
How the hell am I
supposed to know?
You're the leader.
You're supposed to be decisive.
And I've decided
that you should eat
a big bag of dicks, how's that?
You're being facetious,
but if this whole beach
was completely covered in dicks
and somebody said I had to eat
every dick until the beach
was clean for liberty,
I would say no problemo.
Why would someone put penises
all over the beach?
Who knows why madmen
do what they do?
Well, you know what I think?
I think liberty
is just your excuse
to do whatever you want.
Whether that's to eat a beach
full of dicks or killin' folk.
Oh, yeah?
At least I don't kill men
for money like you.
Oh, here we go.
There's something wrong
with your skin.
It's just a rash.
That's a rash?
Oh, no.
You...
are the only one...
fit to carry my javelin.
Carry it for...
Carry it for who?
For what? What the heck?
Who am I supposed
to carry it for?
This is so frustratin'.
He just told me I have
to carry this javelin
for a reason,
but he didn't say why!
Waller? Waller. Waller!
All right, we'll camp here,
and tomorrow we'll go
straight through to the city
to get to La Gatita Amable
by nightfall.
What?
How deep of a sleeper are you?
I was having
the most wonderful dream.
If it was you about to be
eaten by King Shark,
then you're psychic.
I don't believe
he would do that.
He has very kind eyes.
Hungry.
You bastard!
- Uh...
All right,
calm down with the rats!
-What?
-I have a thing with rats.
-You have a thing with rats?
-Yes.
-And you're on a team with me?
-Not something I asked for!
What are you
laughing at me for, man?
Why the fuck are you
in your underwear?
Tighty-whities? Really?
-Now, that's just racist.
- No.
It's not racist.
-They're tighty-whities.
- Oh, come the fuck on.
Bloodsport's got a rat phobia.
-What?
You didn't tell me
you had a fear of rats, DuBois?
I'm an assassin! Why would I
share my liabilities?
For fuck's sake.
Aw. He's offering you
a pretty leaf
to show you he means no harm.
Why the fuck
would I want a leaf?
Just get the rats out of here!
-Oh, fuck's sake.
-Huh. Cool.
Hey, we gonna kill
Megalodouche now, or what?
Nanaue's the strongest
member of your team.
You need him
to get into Jotunheim.
Yeah, well,
we can't function as a team
if we gotta watch our back
from one of our own
eatin' our bollocks.
Nanaue,
would you eat your friends?
I no friends.
You have no friends?
If you did, would you eat them?
Yes.
No?
Then, can we be your friends?
Come on.
He's obviously lying.
If I die
'cause I gambled on love,
it will be a worthy death.
Friends.
You are a little idiot.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God.
I'm good at my job.
I found him.
Check it out.
Look, right here, a mile north.
Task Force X,
you have an additional
mission directive.
We've located
Colonel Rick Flag.
He's been taken by the enemy.
Rick Flag?
I know, you both served
on special forces in Qurac
that took down Avral Kaddam.
Flag was the one
who initially recommended you.
You had
other operatives
and didn't tell us?
There was no tactical
advantage, now there is.
I've uploaded the location
on your MTS.
Terminate his captors
with extreme prejudice.
Kill anyone you see.
These are dangerous people.
Recover Flag before moving on
to the city.
That's where
they're holding Flag.
Nothing like a bloodbath
to start the day.
They call you Peacemaker?
I cherish peace
with all my heart.
I don't care
how many men, women,
and children
I need to kill to get it.
I thought
you were the crazy one.
I am.
All right.
Let's get it.
Boss.
Gracias.
No, no, no!
Hmm?
Non-lethal.
You lose.
Exploding compression bullets.
No one likes a show-off.
Unless what they're
showing off is dope as fuck.
Fuck. That's true.
He does throw
polka dots at people.
I'm sorry it's so...
flamboyant.
It looks cool. I think.
I don't like to kill people,
but if I pretend
they're my mom, it's easy.
T.M.I., mate.
DuBois?
Hey, Flag.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Waller told us that you were...
Uh...
Are you drinkin' tea?
This is Sol Soria,
she's the leader
of the freedom fighters,
the resistance trying to take
down the current government.
They saved my life.
Oh, wow.
Why did my people not alert me
of your arrival?
We didn't see any people.
Yeah, I didn't see
anybody on the way...
There's no one out there.
They were gone
when we got here.
I turned them into my mother
in my head and killed them.
Typical Americans.
Just run in, guns blazing.
I know, this is messed up.
-These guys, they're...
-What's this one do?
They're fucking idiots,
but right now our objectives
align with yours.
If Jotunheim
contains the technology
our intelligence says it does,
then it could be used
on the people of Corto Maltese
as well as Americans.
That's why we need your help
to get into the city
so we can stop 'em.
Is that rat waving at me?
It appears it is.
Why?
I'm gonna guess
because it's friendly.
Luna and Suarez
murdered my entire family.
I'd make a deal
with the Devil to stop them.
Your people will have our help
getting to Valle Del Mar
to apprehend
this Gaius Grieves.
Hey.
-What is this?
-You slaughtered my staff!
They were loyal
to the Herreras.
Who are you loyal to, Thinker?
They call you "Thinker," yes?
All that shit in your face
is to make your brain good?
Yes, makes my brain good.
Are you being sarcastic
with me?
Hey! Hey.
I shall do to you
as we did to your employees.
Hey. Mateo!
What is this?
Project Starfish.
It's been the primary focus
of my experiments here
for the past 30 years.
Here.
What... What is it doing here?
Oh!
It is having little babies.
Not progeny,
extensions of itself.
They take hosts,
and those hosts in turn become
part of the central being.
It feeds
on their consciousnesses.
Grows larger, more powerful.
So...
where is
this Project Starfish now?
Marvelous idea, Presidente.
But as I've noted,
I've been working
with the beast for 30 years.
And there's no one but me
capable of controlling it.
Well, then...
welcome to the team.
Si,  Camila.
Presidente.
You are making
a big mistake
throwing me down here!
I will be outta here
soon enough
and I will kill
every last one of you,
Colto Maltese-tezios.
Maltese-els.
Malte-multoids. Colt-a-mults?
Whatever you  Mario Kart-racing
d-bags are called!
Please.
Put this on.
Oh, wow.
I'm a princess.
Senorita  Quinn,
on behalf of the entire staff
of Our Honorable General
Presidente Silvio
Eleuterio Luna,
it's a pleasure to serve you.
Gracias.
My mother said
to count back again.
Ten, nine,
eight, seven, six,
five, four, three,
two, one. Ha!
Coronel, beat that...
Oh.
Forgive my appearance,
Senorita  Quinn.
I have admired you from afar
for many years now.
Senorita.
Me?
You're a hero to me,
as well as to my people.
I think you might
got me confused.
Harley Quinn's fire
and rebellion
in the face
of American oppression
is something to which
my entire country aspires.
Oh.
I have prepared lunch.
Would you be so kind
as to join me?
I'm so kind, sure.
You're not lonely?
To come and go
Oh, my, you caught my eye
Just irresistible
You're not lonely?
You want me to what?
To marry me.
You're joshing.
Might I be frank, Harley?
You might be.
Good, listen.
Since I took control,
the majority love me.
But some find me to be
an unacceptable leader.
What kinds of dicks
would find that?
Don't they know
how awesome you are?
Have you shown them
the birdies?
It may sound archaic
to someone
from your part of the world,
but my people,
the Corto Malteseans,
they're very old-fashioned.
Corto Malteseans, of course.
And I am a bachelor.
So they want
you to get hitched?
My people say you would
make the perfect wife.
Because, you know,
you symbolize
anti-American fervor.
Oh.
But I am a romantic, Harley.
I agreed to meet with you
just to appease them.
However, upon spending
the day with you,
I find myself hardly able
to think straight.
-You are perfect in every...
-You are so freaking hot.
Just irresistible
Harley Luna.
I like the ring of that.
That's Jotunheim?
Nazis came here seeking asylum
after World War II.
They built Jotunheim
to continue
their unorthodox experiments.
Until the Herrera family
accepted the bounty
and killed them all.
Wowza.
Many years ago,
the rumors began of a beast.
These dark rumors helped
the Herrera family
They would send
their political enemies
and their families
to the fortress,
never to return.
I have recently learned
these were not rumors.
They were murdering thousands
in bizarre experiments
with this creature.
Well, it must be a big relief
to got it
in your hands now, huh?
Absolutely.
Now, it is our enemies
who shall be fearful.
If anyone dares
to say a negative word
about their
new president today,
their parents, their children,
and anyone they ever loved
will be sent to Jotunheim
to feed the beast.
I'm sorry.
Recently, I made
a promise to myself
that the next time
I got a boyfriend,
I'd be on the lookout
for red flags.
And if I saw any,
I would do the healthy thing
and I would murder him.
And killing kids?
Kind of a red flag.
I know, I know.
I know what
you're tryin' to say.
"Harley, why not just leave?"
And I'd say,
"Why are you screaming at me?
"I'm not deaf.
I'm standing right here."
And then I'd say,
"When your taste in men
is as bad as mine,
they don't just
go away quietly.
"They slash your tires
and they kill your dogs and
tell you
that the music you like
ain't real music at all."
And all the cruelty...
...tears you apart
after a while.
You were real pretty and all,
and R.I.P. to that absolutely
beautiful monster
between your legs, but...
all in all...
I think you're
more pretty like this,
with all those rotten thoughts
emptied from your head.
I can't believe
this thing had a bullet.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
What the hell
are you doin'?
We're tired,
Colonel. We need a rest.
Goddamn hobbyists.
We cannot stop.
We need to hurry if you're
going to help my people.
Hey. We're not here
to help your people.
But she's right,
we gotta keep moving.
I carry friend?
It's okay, Nanaue.
It's happening
to his face again.
-It's nothing, I slipped.
-Hey...
Norman Bates, if that shit's
contagious, we need to know.
What is it?
-It's a...
It's an interdimensional virus.
Fuck is that?
My mother was a scientist
at S.T.A.R. Labs,
and she was obsessed
with turning me
and my brothers and sisters
into superheroes.
She infected me.
Now, if I don't, you know,
expel the dots twice a day...
Then what?
They'll eat me alive.
What happened
to your brothers and sisters?
Some lived.
Some...
died.
And your mom, where is she now?
Everywhere.
Okay. Let's move out.
Come on,
we must hurry,
or we'll be late
to meet my contact.
Saying something
They pay you well
Sailing men to...
-Nom, nom!
Are you Milton?
Si.
Milton will drive you
through town
and to La Gatita Amable.
There are clothes in the boxes
for all of you
so you can blend in.
That said, the walking  tiburon
is gonna have
to stay out of sight.
I wear disguise.
Oh, you're going
to wear a disguise.
Si.
Hey, he's learnin' Spanish.
And what kind of disguise?
-Fake mustache.
-Oh.
Yeah, fake mustache
isn't gonna cut it, mate.
There's gonna be a lot of
soldiers watching Jotunheim.
If they discover us there...
Let's pray they do not,
or you will all be dead.
If they do,
that'll leave
the palace vulnerable.
Luna and the other generals
will be left
without protection.
You're a good man,
Colonel Flag.
You still look
exactly like yourself.
That's the worst fake
mustache I've ever seen.
And if you had fooled us,
we'd have to kill you,
shark-shaped bloke
with a moustache
creeping up on us like that.
-You, you.
Aw.
He always wants to be near you.
I think he senses good in you.
Yeah, there's no good in me.
Damn.
Supposed to play golf with
Senator Cray this weekend.
-I'm gonna look a fool.
Waller, come in.
Ugh.
You missed.
Waller, do you copy?
We're losing connection.
Waller.
Fuck's sake.
Task Force X.
-Waller.
You there?
The military must have put
signal jammers around the city.
Your comms are down,
but we can still activate
the bombs,
not to mention what will
happen to your daughter.
So, no funny business.
Do you copy, DuBois?
Copy.
Fuck you!
Hey, uh, all that stuff
about his daughter,
you wouldn't
really do that, right?
You don't know half
of what I would do, John.
What?
Why are you so afraid of rats?
Why are you so in love
with them, Ratcatcher 2?
You know what I think?
I think you have a serious
case of daddy issues.
I have no issues with
how much I loved my father.
Although he was a genius...
we lived homeless
in the streets of Portugal
burdens.
He built the machines
I employ today...
...and taught me the secrets
of calling the rats.
They brought us
trinkets to live on.
And they kept us warm at night,
when we would have frozen.
-But eventually...
-  Papa.
Papa, wake up.
...my father's burdens
became too heavy to carry.
No.
No, Papa.
-And he was gone.
-Papa, wake up.
I took his machinery
and came to America.
That is the dream, right?
But I was arrested
for armed bank robbery,
do you believe it?
The state considered
the rats a weapon.
What?
You remind me of my daughter,
the reason I'm here.
Why are you so afraid of rats?
My old man.
When I was a lad,
if I didn't finish
a task right,
he would dole out
the punishment.
And one day, he just locked me
in a crate for 24 hours.
And it was
full of starvin' rats.
As imperfect my father was...
he loved me.
I wish I could
give that to you.
Don't you worry, yeah?
I'm gonna get you
out of here alive.
I'm going to get you
Senores,
this is the place.
[alternative hip-hop
music playing]
Slipping back
Carsick on a Tuesday
Heartless in a few ways
Elbows shredded
Like too late...
So, when's this Thinker guy
supposed to be here?
Supposed to be
in the next few hours.
Looks like we gotta find
something to do
to pass the time. Uh, miss?
How about some, uh...
What do you guys drink
around here, Fernet?
How about a round of Fernets
for the table.
-Comprende?
-Si.
Hey, Pissmaker,
we're on a mission.
Easy, Inspector Gadget.
A little drink
never hurt nobody.
Except for
the thousands of people
killed in drunk driving
accidents every year.
Come on, DuBois,
this could be our last drink.
Gracias.
Just one.
-You're gonna be that guy?
-I'm gonna be that guy.
Hey,  chica.
Forgot the rat.
Here's to being alive
in three hours.
I'll be alive.
You speak for yourself.
There you go, there you go.
Don't give any more to Polka!
I hope I stay awake
Running, running all day
Everybody's eyes on me
I hope I stay awake
Running, running all day
Everybody's eyes on me
Go. Go.
[hip-hop music playing
on speaker]
That is a gun.
So, smile.
We're old mates who are gonna
take a trip to Jotunheim.
Yup.
Even with my help, you think
you can get into Jotunheim?
Well, if we can't,
I've got a Great White
out back that's looking
for some chum.
Now, come on.
All right, nice and easy.
Oh, fuck.
No, no, no!
All right...
Take him out through the back,
all right.
Find my coordinates in the pad
and meet me in half an hour.
-What?
-Hey, did you hear what I said?
-Yes, but...
-Go.
Let's go.
There's no need
to disturb everyone's night.
I'm right here, I'm the one
you're looking for.
Yep, us too.
We're his American companions.
What?
Ow!
-Come on. Go.
- He...
Oh, God.
-Move it!
Come on!
Hey!
Your equipment
manipulates
animal behavior, clever.
I'm working on something
similar with humans.
Be quiet, please.
You are perceivably panicked.
I'm guessing that you are not
the alphas of this battalion.
Do you want a dozen angry
rodents crawling up your ass?
My answer might not
be what you expect.
Go, go!
The rain sometimes
The roses bloom...
I'm sorry for you.
But soon
you will all be joining
your deranged compatriot,
Harley Quinn.
Is Harley alive?
Not for long.
Mayor General Suarez
can be rather harsh
when extracting information.
Dim mak.
That's
the Cantonese term for it.
In Japan, it's  kyoshu jitsu.
In English,
it's simply the Death Touch,
how to kill a man
with a single blow.
Of course it's possible
to kill a man
with a single blow.
But it's a matter of chance,
and cannot be wielded
with certainty.
-That's what they say.
-They?
-Amateurs.
-On one?
One.
I don't smoke.
The rain sometimes
All right.
Let's go to Jotunheim.
Nope.
There's somethin'
we gotta take care of first.
What?
No...
I will ask again.
How many meta-power teammates
arrived with you
to Corto Maltese?
Sixty-nine.
Sixty-nine?
How could you get
69 troops into the...
Come and rescue me...
You gotta be kiddin' me.
You're gonna risk
the entire mission
for a mental defective
dressed as a court jester.
This coming from a guy
that wears a toilet seat
We don't leave
one of our own behind.
You're okay with this?
No, but I've been around Flag
when he's got a rag
-Best not to tug it.
-Motherfucker!
Hey, wake up, wake up.
All right, let's go.
All right, we'll enter
through the third floor,
go to the inner staircase,
and then down to the cellar
where they usually
keep their detainees.
Hopefully,
Harley's still alive.
It's not a toilet seat,
it's a beacon of freedom!
Selling each romance
When youth will pass away
Say about me
I know they'll say
As life goes on without me
Everywhere I go...
Selling each romance
There's some heart betraying
When youth will pass away
They say about me
I know they'll say
As life goes on without me
All of the time
Nobody cares for me...
That cares for me...
Hola.
Um...
Ratatouille, what do you got?
Third floor hallway's clear.
Abner?
There doesn't seem
to be any incoming traffic.
Bird.
Nanaue, stay off the comm.
Colonel, I got a clean shot
on the only one in the office.
Just give the word.
Fire on three, two...
What are you guys doing?
I... You.
We're here to save you.
You were gonna... save me?
It was a really good plan, too.
Well, I can go back inside,
and you can still do it.
That's patronizing.
Yeah, no, it's not...
Uh,
what's with the javelin?
I'm waitin' for God to tell me.
Jesus Christ.
- Yeah.
Or Him. Or any of them, really.
Okay.
Are you two
all right, yeah?
-I'm so sorry.
-That's all right.
Harley Quinn.
Bloodsport.
All right, who ate
all the fucking empanadas?
Mine were very good.
I had the chicken.
All right,
here's the deal.
We fail the mission, you die.
We find out any information
you give us is false, you die.
If we find out you have
personalized license plates,
What? No.
If you mismatch blacks,
you die.
No.
If you cough without
covering your mouth...
Harley. Those last three
aren't things.
Although, probably
don't need to say this,
but that isn't
an open invitation
for you to cough
without covering your mouth.
All right, we're gonna need
you to drive the minibus,
with all of us inside, past
the guards at the front gate.
Once through the gate,
we'll use you to get through
There are security cameras
everywhere.
They're being dealt with.
We'll neutralize the soldiers
there and enter.
Once we're inside,
we separate into teams.
I am walking back and forth.
Okay. You're gonna lead me
and Ratcatcher 2
I'm going with you
'cause I don't trust this guy.
No, no, no,
you're coming with me.
Our munitions expertise
are needed
starting at the first floor,
going all the way to the top.
Once we're clear, we blow
the tits off that thing,
and go home.
This is suicide.
Well, that's kind of our thing.
Yeah.
This is insane.
Must be a devil between us...
Yeah, no.
I love the rain.
It's like angels
are splooging all over us.
It's good for cover.
Yep, that too.
-You son of a bit...
Input
the emergency code. Now!
Well, go on then!
Yo!
Okay, Pokey.
You get a bomb, you get a bomb.
Harley and I
will meet you up
Yeah? All right.
God damn it,
Nanaue.
No!
Quit bein' a play baby.
Peacemaker.
-It's actually very nice.
Just put it against the wall.
It looks nothin' like me.
Move. Move it.
This way.
Si.
Vamonos. Vamonos!
Good God.
If God existed,
wouldn't this be proof
that he wasn't good at all?
What the hell is this?
I thought you were looking
for Project Starfish.
You've brought us visitors,
have you, Grieves?
Have you come to save me
from that madman?
Thirty years he's kept me here.
Tortured me.
Had his way with me.
I call it Starro the Conqueror.
That's meant to be derisive.
Sorry, old chum.
These two are here to kill you.
It's out of my hands.
We need to help these people.
Impossible, dear. They're
corpses below those stars.
Who are they?
The fodder of powerful men
through every age.
Dissidents,
journalists,
political rivals,
and their loved ones.
Oh, please,
unclutch your fucking pearls,
Flag.
We serve the same master.
We were sent here to stop you.
Child,
your government
didn't send you here
to protect the world
from alien technology.
Your government sent you here
to cover up their part in it.
You're a goddamn liar.
American goddamn astronauts
found Starro.
Yankee-fucking-doodle dandies.
Although the Cold War
was ended,
your government
saw the potential
in weaponizing
such a powerful beast,
but banish the thought
of any such experiments
being held on American soil.
Your people
have always been squeamish
about the sacrifices necessary
for scientific advancement.
So,
the United States
made a secret deal
with the Corto Maltese
government
to conduct
their illegal experiments here
in Jotunheim.
And they hired me
to oversee them.
And now, because of
a run-of-the-mill
fucking military coup,
they're gonna destroy
30 years' worth of efforts.
Yeah!
You're the real victim here.
The hell you doing here?
You're supposed to be upstairs
I told you I didn't trust him.
Your records are located
in those computers?
Colonel, what are you doing?
I joined the military
to serve my country,
not to be its puppet.
What are you doing?
Who are you going
to show that to?
The press. Goddamn people
deserve to know.
I'm tired of coverin' up
their dirty little secrets.
This time
these sons of bitches
I can't let you do that,
Colonel.
-Excuse me?
-I'm truly sorry.
Miss Waller charged me
with makin' sure
those records
don't leave this building.
Of course, I shoulda known.
Waller's always got a backup.
Come on, man,
this isn't personal.
Holdin' a gun on me
is pretty fucking personal.
What is that?
I'm gonna need that drive,
Colonel.
Those morons set off
the explosives too early.
Hand over the drive!
-Let's go, come on!
They experimented on children.
No one is sayin'
what they did was right.
They experimented on children!
That information gets out,
it causes
an international incident!
Keepin' the peace
is worth any price,
including the life
of a hero like yours, sir,
so please...
don't make me do this.
What have you people done?
Sebastian, come!
Okay, we gotta calm down.
Let's all just...
Let's talk about this.
I understand
where you're coming from.
I crossed a line.
Okay, I crossed a line!
I realize that,
but I'm ready to change.
I am ready to change.
And I didn't
mean to hurt you...
You motherfucker.
Peacemaker.
What a joke.
Cleo.
Give me back the drive.
I told you that information
can't get out. Fuck!
So, okay, okay,
destroy the hard drive.
-Why kill me?
Because I'm thorough.
-Oh, my...
Sorry, kid.
No, no...
All right, troops are coming.
This floor, and then
nine floors left. Let's go!
-Come on!
New dumb friends.
Aw, fizzle sticks. Hold on.
Has anyone got eyes
or ears on any more?
They killed Milton!
Milton was still with us?
-Where'd you think he was?
- I don't know.
I thought he stayed back
with the bus.
What was Milton gonna do?
He was helping us!
-Who's Milton?
-What?
I don't remember any Milton.
Fuck! He has been with us
the whole time.
Somebody named Milton
has been with us
Yes!
I don't think so.
I think I would've noticed
if a guy named Milton's
been with us.
It's not a very common name.
I don't think
I've ever even met Milton.
Are you messing around
right now?
He was a really nice guy,
and he sacrificed himself
to help us.
And now look at him.
He's dead.
Oh, that guy!
Milton, Milton.
So, when did this great
love affair with Milton start?
I liked him
from the beginning, okay?
I just didn't say
anything until...
No!
Harley!
Give us a hand!
Hey!
Vamos. Vamos.
Oh!
Oh, fuck, fuck.
Oh, fuck off!
-Oh.
Sorry, kid.
No, no, no.
Smaller bullets.
He killed Colonel Flag.
He wanted to share this
with the press.
It's proof
the American government
was behind Project Starfish
the whole time.
Whoa. Whoa.
I think it's trying to get out.
-What?
-Starro the...
Whoa.
Cover your faces!
Si.
-Whoa.
-What the fuck is that?
Uh... Hey, guys?
Oh, shit, there's...
This city is mine.
Uh, Miss Waller,
I think the feed is back up.
Oh, my God, Miss Waller!
We've got a freaking  kaiju
up in this shit!
Task force X, come in.
Are you there?
Uh-huh.
Whatever signal jammers
were blocking
our communications
must have been in the building
you just demolished.
Yeah, well, we've got a mite
issue over here, Waller.
It's Project Starfish,
Miss Waller.
It's headed towards the city,
and I think it wants
to feed on as many people
as it can.
Not our problem.
If you've destroyed Jotunheim
and the records within,
you've achieved the objective.
Corto Maltese
is no longer a U.S. ally.
If anything,
the White House will consider
fomenting disruption
in a hostile nation
a positive development.
You heard what she said.
Fuck.
Bloodsport is off mission.
What the...
She'll kill you, you know.
That's her business.
I knew Sebastian sensed good
in you for a reason.
Just keep that fucking rat
away from me.
Ratcatcher is also off mission.
Bloodsport, Ratcatcher,
turn around.
Nanaue!
I know what I'm carrying
the javelin for.
Krill, turn around now!
Turn back now, God damn it!
-Open it.
-Miss Waller...
Open it!
What are you doing,
Task Force X?
-Fuck!
Turn around now, God damn it!
You dumb pieces of shit!
Motherfuckers!
God damn it, Task Force X,
this is your last
motherfucking warning!
Oh, my God!
What the fuck did you do?
All those people, John.
Little kids.
Task Force X, the creature
is headed to Calle Principal.
Avoid Avenida Medrano.
-There is a swarm of infected.
- Jesus.
So, your clearest path
is Calle Aguero.
Get on the satellite, Dale,
you fucking dickhead!
Yes, ma'am.
Huh?
Harley, take the high ground!
Nanaue! Monster is nom nom!
Monster nom nom?
Yes!
Abner, do you see who that is?
Huh?
It's your mom!
I'm a superhero!
I'm a motherfucking super...
God!
No! No!
Oh, no...
This city
is mine!
This city isn't yours.
This city isn't ours.
This city is theirs.
Oh, hell.
Why rats, Papa?
Rats are the lowliest
and most despised
of all creatures, my love.
If they have purpose,
so do we all.
I was happy,
floating, staring at the stars.
A group of escaped convicts
saved a city of millions
on the small island nation
of Corto Maltese today.
That's my dad.
Because of these people,
Corto Maltese will have
free democratic elections
for the first time in 90 years.
Viva Corto Maltese!
Viva Corto Maltese! Viva...
-That's my dad.
-...Corto Maltese! Viva...
Yeah.
Oh, that's just a taste
of what's on that drive.
I've uploaded it all
to a secure server.
Now, if you kill any one of us,
or my daughter ever sees
the inside of a prison,
it goes public.
If we all go free,
it never has to see
the light of day.
I told you I'd make you
a leader, DuBois.
You got a deal.
Nanaue.
Look, I know Flag wanted to
give the drive to the press,
but we just saved
a whole bloody city.
We can't have it all.
Flag was my friend.
Mine too.
And I haven't got
many of those.
I could be your friend, Milton.
Not my name.
What?
What are you talkin' about?
We just had a conversation
for, like, three hours
about how your name is Milton.
Didn't.
Yes, we did.
No. Our ride's here.
-Hmm.
Nom nom?
Really?
That is what you're
thinkin' about right now?
No. That nom nom though.
No, it's not nom nom.
No!
About a fancy car
Me to you
About how far you are
Come through for you
Another birthday party
When we're older
Just a dream
To be loved by you
To be loved by you, by you
In the sky again
To the diaphragm
And lie again, whoa
You're my nightmare
She don't fight fair
That you'd notice my despair
I don't care 'cause
The violence
They invite the silence
I need some guidance
Don't stand a chance
The upper hand
I'm a sick joke
And I can't cope
Poke with my kinfolk
I'm a sick joke
And I can't cope
'Cause it broke, whoo!
The upper hand
Said they found him
in the rubble.
They were shocked
his heart was still beating.
I wasn't certain
how safe it was,
shipping him back here.
But, if anything,
he's shown he's resilient.
It'll take some surgery,
but eventually we'll get him
back up to speed.
You realize
this is revenge, right?
Waller knows
we double-crossed her,
and she's getting back at us
by saddling us
with this douchebag.
Yep.
I heard he was sort of a hero
down in Corto Maltese.
Oh, is that what you heard?
Because not quite.
What do you guys
want him for?
Just to save
the fucking world, that's all.